# EMIR HALICI

# Flutter Developer

# DETAILS

- 🔘 Gölbaşı, Ankara / İlkadım, Samsun
- emir.halici1@gmail.com
- github.com/emirhalici
- in linkedin.com/in/emirhalici/

# LANGUAGES

Turkish Native
English Professional Efficiency

# **SKILLS**

Flutter

Figma

Java

C#

#### **PROFILE**

Flutter developer and full time computer engineering student with months of experience from personal projects.

With the start of my education, I have started my journey with Python and C. With my own interests and curiosity, I went on to learn **Android Dev** with **Java** for 5 months and finally I landed on cross-platform development with **Flutter/Dart**. You can find my example projects and personal growth on my **github** profile.

#### **EDUCATION**

Computer Engineering, Bachelor's Degree, 3rd Year

2020/2024

Current GPA: 3.35/4.00

## **EMPLOYMENT**

Flutter Developer Intern @ Coreborn

June 2022 - July 2022

- -Developed Flutter apps and resolved issues in Flutter projects.
- -Worked closely with GraphQL, Hasura, Heroku...
- -Wrote **Medium** posts about work I've done.
- -Used **Git** extensively; opened and closed issues, created and merged pull requests as needed.

Summer Student Job as Cashier

June 2020 - September 2020 May 2021 - September 2021

## **PORTFOLIO**

#### English Dictionary App

Flutter/Dart

- -A multi-screen english word bank app with built-in pop quiz.
- -Used packages: sqflite, provider, http...

#### Instacione App 🔼

Flutter/Dart

- -A complete working clone of Instragram powered with Firebase.
- -Used packages: <a href="mailto:provider">provider</a>, <a href="firebase\_auth">firebase\_core</a>, <a href="firebase\_storage">firebase\_storage</a>, <a href="permission\_handler">permission\_handler</a>, <a href="firebase\_storage">flutter\_screenutil</a>...

#### Simple Todo App

Flutter/Dart

-A simple todo app built by me at my Coreborn internship. The goal was to be familiar with GraphQL engines, Hasura and Heroku.

-Used packages: **provider**, **graphql**, **numberpicker**, **flutter\_svg**, **fluttertoast**, **flutter\_screenutil**...